onehanesplace.com 2010-10-17

# One Hanes Place – Outlet Prices, Great Selection !!

At Hanesbrands Inc. ("Hanesbrands"), we respect our customers and understand that you may have concerns about privacy, so we have instituted privacy policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly.

This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the privacy policy pertaining to this website, **onehanesplace.com** (the "Site"), which is owned by Hanesbrands Inc. ("Hanesbrands") and to other Internet sites on which this Privacy Policy is posted. Hanesbrands is a consumer goods company with a portfolio of leading apparel brands, including _Hanes, Champion, Playtex, Bali, Just My Size, barely there and Wonderbra_. Hanesbrands and it affiliates design, manufacture, source and sell a broad range of apparel essentials such as t-shirts, bras, panties, men’s underwear, kids’ underwear, socks, hosiery, casualwear and activewear. Hanesbrands markets directly to consumers through retail outlets, catalogs and websites, with multiple websites, catalog titles and retail stores. By using this Site, you expressly accept and agree to be bound by and abide by the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement. For other terms and conditions that apply to your use of the Site, please review our [Terms of Use](http://www.onehanesplace.com/webapp/commerce/command/ExecMacro/info.d2w/report?info=legal).

Any terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy Statement shall have the meaning given in the Terms of Use. This Privacy Policy Statement applies only to "Personal Information" (as defined below) that we collect on-line. Unless otherwise provided herein, any reference to "Hanesbrands," "we," "us" and "our" shall mean and include Hanesbrands and its affiliates. 

**Overview: This Privacy Policy Statement is intended to explain our privacy practices and inform you as to:**

  * The kinds of Personal Information we collect from users of the Site and how that information is collected; 
  * How we use your Personal Information; 
  * The circumstances under which we disclose Personal Information to third parties; 
  * How you can access, update or delete any Personal Information collected about you by us; and 
  * The mechanisms we have implemented to protect your Personal Information. 

**Information Hanesbrands Collects**

For purposes of this Privacy Policy Statement, "Personal Information" means any information which you provide to us to a non-public area or section of the Site by which you can be personally identified, and may include your first/middle initial or name and last name, street address, town or city,state, zip code, telephone number, instant-messenger nickname, blog,\ or other personal website URL, date of birth,e-mail address, credit card or debit card information and any other information. Your credit card or debit card number is classified as sensitive Personal Information and is colledted via a secure transmission. Examples of non-public areas of our Site include private wish list registries, registration pages and email subscription pages. Hanesbrands collects Personal Information about you only when you submit it to us, such as when subscribing to our e-mail program, purchasing products, submitting a testimonial or question, participating in special functions of the Site, such as e-cards, wish lists or games, responding to a survey, entering a sweepstakes, or making suggestions or comments, or requesting a catalog.

Besides Personal Information, when you access the Site our web servers may automatically recognize and collect information regarding your referring domain, your type of internet browser, operating system software, screen resolution, cookie preferences and similar technical data. None of this information is personally identifiable and we use this information only in the aggregate, to measure overall Site usage patterns and trends.

We recognize the particular importance of protecting the privacy of Personal Information where children are involved. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If a child under the age of 13 has provided our website with personally identifiable information, we ask that such child's parent or guardian call 1-800-671-5056 or contact us at [ohp.manager@onehanesplace.com](http://www.onehanesplace.com/webapp/commerce/command/ExecMacro/info.d2w/report?info=CustServEmail) and we will delete the information about the child from our files. 

If we publish Postings that you submit to us for potential publication, we may identify you as the source of such information by first name, last initial and city of residence or as otherwise indicated on the applicable submission pages. Any information about yourself submitted in a "public" area of our Site and/or other areas or features, may allow members of the general public to view such submitted information and content on the Internet, may be routed through our servers, the servers of one or more third parties on our behalf, and the Internet, **and you have no expectation of or right to privacy with regard to any such Posting**. We have no obligation to monitor any Postings, particularly as to the content of e-cards or similar features where visitors have the option of creating a message. Such public areas and features offered therein are public and not private communications. The security of any information you disclose is not guaranteed; you make such Postings and disclosures at your own risk. We are not responsible for any errors, omissions, or offensive material contained in any content posted in any public areas or any decisions made or actions taken or not taken based on such information or content.

**Accuracy and Confidentiality**

It is your responsibility to give us current, complete, truthful and accurate information and to keep the Personal Information that you provide to us up to date. **We cannot and will not be responsible for any problems or liability that may arise if you do not give us accurate, truthful or complete information or you fail to update the information you give us.**

You are solely responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your user name and password, if applicable, and for any charges, costs, expenses, damages, liabilities and losses we incur or may suffer as a result of your failure to do so. You, and not us, are solely responsible and liable for your activity, behavior, use and conduct on the Site and for any use of the Site or any other activity or conduct in connection with the Site, by any others who use your user name or password, unless and until you notify us that your user name or password may have been compromised, misappropriated or improperly taken or used by another party.

**Links to Other Sites**

The Site may contain advertisements, references and links to other websites and third parties. We may also use third parties to display or serve advertising on the Site and our web-based newsletters or other communications which you may choose to receive. Often these third party advertisers employ cookie and web bug technologies to measure advertising effectiveness. You should be aware that different rules might apply to the collection, use or disclosure of your information by third parties in connection with their advertisements, promotions and websites you encounter on the Internet. The use of such technology by these third parties is within their control and not ours. Even if we have a relationship with the third party, we do not control those sites or their policies and practices regarding your information. **_This Privacy Policy Statement does not cover any use of Personal Information that a third party advertiser or ad server may collect from you._** We encourage you to investigate and ask questions directly of them in this regard. Use of advertisers’ tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Security**

We maintain reasonable standards of security and confidentiality. However, for most Internet sites, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications over an unsecured transmission. We conduct financial transactions via secured transmissions but may not always secure other parts of the Site. We also limit access to the Site by our own employees to those individuals who are authorized for the proper handling of such information and any employee found violating our standards of security and confidentiality will be subject to our disciplinary processes. We request that our operational service providers follow the same policy.

**Phishing**

Phishing attacks attempt to steal consumers’ personal identity data and financial account credentials. “Phishers” use “spoofed” e-mails to lead consumers to counterfeit websites designed to trick recipients into divulging sensitive Personal Information such as credit card numbers, account usernames, passwords, and Social Security Numbers. **WE DO NOT SEND EMAILS ASKING YOU TO PROVIDE OR CONFIRM SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION OR YOUR USERNAME OR PASSWORD!** If you receive such e-mail communication, please forward it immediately to the Site’s Privacy Administrator at ohp.manager@onehanesplace.com, and then immediately delete the fraudulent e-mail from your computer.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We may use a technology called "cookies" to provide you with tailored information. A cookie is a small piece of data that the Site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so our Site can recognize you as you browse the Site and when you return. These cookies may collect the type of operating system and browser that you are using, and accumulate and report anonymous, statistical information on Site usage. The use of cookies shows how our customers navigate through our web site and thus allows us to make our Site more responsive to your needs, by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. We do not use cookies to identify or track any Personal Information. If you do not wish to have a cookie sent to your browser, you can change the settings on your Internet browser to stop it from automatically accepting cookies. While rejecting a cookie will not normally affect your browsing or your ability to access the features on our Site, you may be required to re-enter certain information when you browse or when you return to the Site. If you are experiencing trouble browsing our site, it is possible that you did not accept or have configured your browser to block cookies from the Site.

We also may use electronic image requests (also called "web beacons" or "single-pixel gifs") to count page views and to access cookies. The web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any Personal Information; they are used only to compile anonymous information about Site usage.

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

We do not sell, rent, lease or disclose your Personal Information to unaffiliated entities or entities that are not our advertisers, except in the limited circumstances listed below. When we plan to disclose your Personal Information to advertisers, we ask for you to opt-in to do so, in which case their use of your information is subject to the advertisers’ own privacy policies. We may disclose Personal Information to affiliates for marketing and/or administrative purposes and you will have the right to opt-out of such disclosure for marketing purposes.

**How Hanesbrands Uses the Information**

Except for Personal Information which you submit to a public area or section of our Site, it is our policy to maintain all Personal Information as confidential except as may be necessary to fulfill a function or purpose such as those listed below: 

  * for the specific purpose for which it was submitted (for example, to enter a sweepstakes, submit a testimonial, or to receive product information) 
  * to post on the Site, testimonials, photographs, questions, comments, or other information that you may submit to us for potential publication, subject to any disclosure or other terms and conditions found on the submission page and our [Terms of Use](http://www.onehanesplace.com/webapp/commerce/command/ExecMacro/info.d2w/report?info=legal). 
  * to improve the content, appearance and utility of the Site 
  * to trace our visitors' use of the Site for internal research purposes 
  * to contact you to participate in market research which you have agreed to receive 
  * to notify our visitors of updates to the Site 
  * to send catalogs, printed materials, offers and other announcements to your home address and to allow our affiliates and other reputable third party marketers to do the same 
  * to send e-mail offers, announcements, or newsletters to your e-mail address and to allow our affiliates to do the same 
  * to provide any necessary notices to our visitors 

Additionally, we may disclose specific information about you in our possession upon governmental request or if required to do so by law or based on our belief, in our sole discretion, that it is necessary to conform to or comply with our legal and regulatory obligations or is necessary to protect our Site, our business and assets, the users of our Site or the public, in general. 

On occasion, we contract with other companies to provide certain services to us, including credit card processing, shipping, e-mail distribution, changing mailing addresses, market research and promotions management. We provide these companies only with the information needed to perform their services (which may include Personal Information) and work closely with them to ensure that your Personal Information is maintained and used as set forth in this Privacy Policy Statement. These companies are prohibited from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with others, but we cannot guarantee security of Personal Information and are not liable for misuse of it by others.

Hanesbrands may (a) buy or sell assets, subsidiaries, or business units, or may be acquired by another company or (b) file for or be subject to an involuntary bankruptcy or restructuring. In such transactions, Personal Information is usually one of the transferred business assets, and we reserve the right to transfer all Personal Information in our possession as part of any such transaction. Such transferred Personal Information shall remain subject to the promises made in this Privacy Policy Statement.

Provided that you register on our Site, except for Personal Information needed to complete your purchase of products, if any, and in the event the Site does not have a “My Account” link to pages containing the Personal Information you wish to access, you may request that: (i) we correct or update any such Personal Information; (ii) such Personal Information not be provided to third parties; or (iii) such Personal Information be removed from our active marketing databases. To make such a request, you may [click here](http://www.onehanesplace.com/webapp/commerce/command/ExecMacro/info.d2w/report?info=CustServEmail) or send an e-mail to ohp.manager@onehanesplace.com; write to P.O. Box 748, Rural Hall, NC 27098-0748; write to One Hanes Place Consumer Services, Hanesbrands Inc., P.O. Box 748, Rural Hall, NC 27098, or call toll free 1-800-671-5056. When contacting us, please be sure to provide us with your exact e-mail address, name, postal address, and/or telephone number(s) in order to be sure we handle your request correctly. Please also note that each time we send you an e-mail message, we will give you the option to unsubscribe from our e-mail list by simply clicking the unsubscribe link. However, we may continue to contact you via e-mail for administrative or informational purposes, including follow-up messages regarding the administration of your account, any services, features or functions you have enrolled in or registered to use, any promotions or contests you have participated in or have entered, goods and/or services you have ordered, or other transactions you have undertaken with the Site.

**Updating the Privacy Policy Statement**

As we continue to develop our Site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, we may have a need to change our current privacy policies. We therefore reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy Statement at any time. This Privacy Policy Statement is effective on and was last updated July 10, 2008. If elements of our Privacy Policy Statement change, we will revise this Privacy Policy Statement. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy Statement will mean that you accept those changes.

**Questions Regarding the Privacy Policy Statement**

To all other users of the Site, if you have other questions or inquiries about this Privacy Policy Statement, please contact our Privacy Administrator via e-mail at [ohp.manager@onehanesplace.com](http://www.onehanesplace.com/webapp/commerce/command/ExecMacro/info.d2w/report?info=CustServEmail) call 1-800-671-5056 or mail your question or inquiry to: 

**Hanesbrands Inc.  
P.O. Box 748  
Rural Hall, NC 27098  
c/o Privacy Administrator**

© Hanesbrands Inc. All Rights Reserved.
